Roxane Connick Carlisle collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Photographs, Due to the small space in which to write on the slide mats, some of the information is unclear or difficult to understand. Carlisle's spelling of proper names of locations or ethnic groups reflect contemporary spelling. In these cases, the first instance is revised to reflec
  - Subseries 13: Upper Nile Province - Sudan, 1963; Malakal; general views of town; Governor Osman Nasr at home; District Commissioner Emin el Tinay
    - Sayed el Tinay's daughter; Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Ektachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0850 (Box 10)
    - Emin el Tinay's garden; Kodoc, Shilluk Territory, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0851 (Box 10)
    - Courtyard in front of district commissioner's house in Kodoc, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0852 (Box 10)
    - Prisoner's hut before Emin el Tinay's house in Kodoc, Shilluk Territory, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0853 (Box 10)
    - Prisoners at work [?], 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0854 (Box 10)
    - Prisoners at work [?], 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0855 (Box 10)
    - Possibly part of the prison stockade, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0856 (Box 10)
    - Police and administrators headquarters at Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0857 (Box 10)
    - Administrators buildings Kodoc (district commissioner's office and police) Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0858 (Box 10)
    - Street in Kodoc - prisoners returning to their stockade after work, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0859 (Box 10)
    - Prison stockade, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0860 (Box 10)
    - Prisoners repairing levees at Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0861 (Box 10)
    - Prisoners repairing levees at Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0862 (Box 10)
    - Levees at Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0863 (Box 10)
    - Ferry at Malakal dock, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0864 (Box 10)
    - Prisoners repairing levees at Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0865 (Box 10)
    - Prisoners repairing levees at Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0866 (Box 10)
    - Prisoners repairing levees [?], 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0867 (Box 10)
    - Ferry at Malakal dock, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0868 (Box 10)
    - Member of the military escort [?], 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0869 (Box 10)
    - Member of the military escort [?], 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0870 (Box 10)
    - Member of the military escort [?], 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0871 (Box 10)
    - Members of the military escort [?], 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0872 (Box 10)
  - Subseries 14: Upper Nile Province - Sudan 1963; Akura and Fashoda, sites of the sacred shrines in Nyikang with Reth and guards and priests
    - Military escort to Shilluk area out of Kodoc - to Akurwa Governor Nasr's man, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0873 (Box 10)
    - Libations over grave at village near Akurwa, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0874 (Box 10)
    - Pouring libations over grave of dead at Shilluk funeral, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0875 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk magic to route evil before hut of deceased, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0876 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk before funeral hut north of Kodoc; Upper Nile Province, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0877 (Box 10)
    - Dancers gathering at a Akurwa for ritual, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0878 (Box 10)
    - Dancers at Akurwa, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0879 (Box 10)
    - Horn players at Akurwa, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0880 (Box 10)
    - Drummers at Akurwa, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0881 (Box 10)
    - Reth at Akurwa, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0882 (Box 10)
    - Reth at Akurwa, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0883 (Box 10)
    - Reth at Akurwa, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0884 (Box 10)
    - Reth at Akurwa, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0885 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk at Akurwa, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0886 (Box 10)
    - Edward Umum of Lelo and his ancestors's Ago Ri chief necklaces; Lelo village, Shilluk Territory, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0887 (Box 10)
    - Road from Akurwa to Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0888 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk village near Malakal, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0889 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk village near Malakal, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0890 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk thom player William Owsti; Malakal, Upper Nile Province, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0891 (Box 10)
      A thom is a type of guitar.
    - Shilluk thom player William Owsti; Malakal, Upper Nile Province, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0892 (Box 10)
      See the note for PH0891.
    - Shilluk thom; Tonga, near Malakal, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0893 (Box 10)
    - Athurwic mound at Fashoda, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0894 (Box 10)
    - Athurwic mound at Fashoda, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0895 (Box 10)
    - Reth Kur Fafiti at Fashoda, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0896 (Box 10)
    - Reth Kur Fafiti walking to shrine of Nyikang at Fashoda, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0897 (Box 10)
    - Nyikang shrine at Fashoda, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0898 (Box 10)
    - Women plaiting roof rings from reeds at Fashoda for Nyikang's kitchen hut, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0899 (Box 10)
    - Workers on Nyikang's kitchen hut at Fashoda, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0900 (Box 10)
    - Close-up image of a man, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0901 (Box 10)
    - Close-up image of a man, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0902 (Box 10)
    - Close-up image of a man, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0903 (Box 10)
    - District commissioner's truck for me at Fashoda; Shilluk Territory; Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0904 (Box 10)
    - Entrance to Fashoda, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0905 (Box 10)
    - Fashoda privacy fence, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0906 (Box 10)
    - Athurwic at Fashoda, Shilluk area near Kodoc Upper Nile, Sudan, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0907 (Box 10)
    - Reth, district commissioner's man, Edward Owati escorts at Fashoda, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0908 (Box 10)
    - Priestess of Nyikang; Fashoda, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0909 (Box 10)
    - Reth at Nyikang's shrine; Fashoda, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0910 (Box 10)
    - Priestess of Nyikang; Fashoda, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0911 (Box 10)
    - Nyikang's attendants; Fashoda, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0912 (Box 10)
    - Nyikang's attendant; Fashoda, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0913 (Box 10)
    - Priestess of Nyikang; Fashoda, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0914 (Box 10)
    - Priests and priestess at Nyikang's shrine; Fashoda, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0915 (Box 10)
    - Nyikang's shrine; Fashoda, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0916 (Box 10)
    - Nyikang's shrine; Fashoda; Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0917 (Box 10)
    - Nyikang's shrine; Fashoda; Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0918 (Box 10)
    - Repair reeds for shrine of Nyikang, Fashoda, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0919 (Box 10)
    - Entrance to shrine of Nyikang at Fashoda, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0920 (Box 10)
    - Entrance to shrine of Nyikang; Fashoda, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0921 (Box 10)
    - Erection of kitchen hut for Nyikang at Fashoda, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0922 (Box 10)
    - Leaving Nyikang's shrine at Fashoda, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0923 (Box 10)
    - Reth atop his home mound at Fashoda hut being prepared, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0924 (Box 10)
    - Leaving Reth's hut complex at Fashoda, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0925 (Box 10)
    - Reth at Fashoda, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0926 (Box 10)
    - Reth at Fashoda, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0927 (Box 10)
  - Subseries 15: Upper Nile Province - Sudan 1963; Kodoc, the court with the Reth Kur Fafiti; District Commissioner Emin el Tinay; Malakal views
    - Shilluk dugouts; Upper Nile Province, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0928 (Box 10)
    - Reth's drum at Kodor, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0929 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk dugouts; Upper Nile Province, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0930 (Box 10)
    - Reth's drum at Kodoc; Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0931 (Box 10)
    - Reth's drum at Kodoc; Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0932 (Box 10)
    - People standing and sitting on a porch, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0933 (Box 10)
    - Reth's drum at Kodoc; Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0934 (Box 10)
    - Dancers [?], 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0935 (Box 10)
    - Reth Kur Fafiti and Shilluk singers at Kodoc, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0936 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk spears [?], 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0937 (Box 10)
    - Emin el Tinay at Kodoc; Upper Nile Province, Sudan, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0938 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk dancers at Kodoc; Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0939 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk women leading the men dance pantomime at Kodoc; Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0940 (Box 10)
    - Two men, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0941 (Box 10)
      See PH0946.
    - Shilluk drum maker's house near Malakal, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0942 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk drum maker's house near Malakal, May 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0943 (Box 10)
    - People by the river, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0944 (Box 10)
    - Young man leading donkey, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0945 (Box 10)
    - Two men, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0946 (Box 10)
      See PH0941.
    - Compound [?], 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0947 (Box 10)
      See PH0950.
    - Men sitting in the shade, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0948 (Box 10)
    - Emin el Tinay's shaking hands with Reth Kur Fafiti at Kodoc, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0949 (Box 10)
    - Compound [?], 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0950 (Box 10)
      See the PH0947.
    - Reth of Shilluk's drum; Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0951 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk washing in river in Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0952 (Box 10)
    - Water hyacinths at Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0953 (Box 10)
    - Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0954 (Box 10)
    - Kodoc road to river; Shilluk Territory, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0955 (Box 10)
    - Massed Shilluk dancers for World Health Org. celebrating; Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0956 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk dancers celebrating World Health Organization Day at Kodoc, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0957 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk at boat landing; Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0958 (Box 10)
    - Maneuvering a log onto a patient donkey; Shilluk at Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0959 (Box 10)
    - A "modern" Shilluk; Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0960 (Box 10)
    - Reth of Shilluk at dusk gathering for dance celebrating World Health Organization Day; Kodoc, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0961 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk Singer; Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0962 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk Singers at Kodoc, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0963 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk Singers at Kodoc, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0964 (Box 10)
    - Reth Kur Papiti of Shilluk; Kodoc; Shilluk Territory, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Ektachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0965 (Box 10)
    - Reth Kur Papiti of Shilluk; Kodoc; Shilluk Territory, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Ektachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0966 (Box 10)
    - Reth Kur Papiti in home of district commissioner el Tinay Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Ektachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0967 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk Singer; Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0968 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk Singer; Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0969 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk Singer; Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0970 (Box 10)
    - Reth Kur Papiti at court in Kodoc with Shilluk, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0971 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk palaver court; Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0972 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk at Kodoc recording session, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0973 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk in Kodoc, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0974 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk in Kodoc; trucks, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0975 (Box 10)
    - Street in Kodoc, Upper Nile Province, April 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0976 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk village; Upper Nile Province, Sudan, April 1963, 1 slide (duplicate): black and white; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0977 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk Reth at Kodoc (dark); Sudan, April 1963, 35 mm slide; color; Kodachrome; AFC 2012/008: PH0978 (Box 10)
    - Reth of Shilluk (close-up); Sudan, April 1963, 35 mm slide; color; Kodachrome; AFC 2012/008: PH0979 (Box 10)
    - Two people standing in the foreground, and several people in the background, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0980 (Box 10)
    - Dancers with spears, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0981 (Box 10)
    - Dancers with spears, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0982 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk man [?], 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0983 (Box 10)
    - Shilluk man [?], 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0984 (Box 10)
  - Subseries 16: Yahia wedding - Omdurman; views of preparations, and of the sisters and family at prayers, and before the first night's party; Yahia family at home; Sakina's wedding
    - Yahia house; Omdurman; Wedding preparations, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0985 (Box 10)
    - Yahia house; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0986 (Box 10)
    - Lunch for me at Yahia home, Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0987 (Box 10)
    - Leila and Naima Yahia; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0988 (Box 10)
    - Yahia sisters; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0989 (Box 10)
    - Yahia sisters: ?, Leila, Naima, Sakina, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0990 (Box 10)
    - Both Leilas - cousins; Yahia, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0991 (Box 10)
    - Yahia cousins Sakina and Leila, Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0992 (Box 10)
    - Leila Yahia; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0993 (Box 10)
    - Leila Yahia; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0994 (Box 10)
    - Naima Yahia, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0995 (Box 10)
    - Naima Yahia and servant, morning of Sakina's wedding, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0996 (Box 10)
    - Yahia mother; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0997 (Box 10)
    - Mahmoud Yahia; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0998 (Box 10)
    - Leila, fiancée of Mahmoud Yahia; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0999 (Box 10)
    - Mohammed Yahia; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Ektachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1000 (Box 10)
    - Mohammed fiancée and cousin at Yahia entrance gate; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1001 (Box 11)
    - Mohammed's fiancée Yahia; women's gate to compound, Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1002 (Box 11)
    - Mohammed's fiancée at Yahia wedding; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1003 (Box 11)
    - Mohammed's fiancée at Yahia wedding; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1004 (Box 11)
    - Leila in passage to men's side of Yahia house; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1005 (Box 11)
    - Chairs arriving for Yahia wedding, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1006 (Box 11)
    - Yahia wedding, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1007 (Box 11)
    - Chairs for Yahia wedding, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1008 (Box 11)
    - Chairs for Sakina's wedding in Yahia compound, Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1009 (Box 11)
    - Yahia wedding; chairs, figures, in alleyway; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1010 (Box 11)
    - Yahia wedding preparations; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1011 (Box 11)
    - Soldiers placing roof lights for Sakina's wedding; Yahia compound. Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1012 (Box 11)
    - Ice for Yahia wedding; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1013 (Box 11)
    - Yahia wedding preparations; Yahia mother in blue tob; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1014 (Box 11)
    - Ice and soft drinks for Yahia wedding; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1015 (Box 11)
    - Coals ready to broil wedding meat; Yahia compound, Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1016 (Box 11)
    - Wedding food; Yahia compound, Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1017 (Box 11)
    - Cooks preparing Yahia wedding supper; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1018 (Box 11)
    - Cooks preparing Yahia wedding food; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1019 (Box 11)
    - Lamb hearts for Yahia wedding; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1020 (Box 11)
    - Yahia cook preparing food in compound lane, Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1021 (Box 11)
    - Food preparation in Yahia house; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1022 (Box 11)
    - Sausages for wedding dinner; Yahia household, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1023 (Box 11)
    - Mohammed's father praying; Yahia; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1024 (Box 11)
    - Mohammed Yahia's father and relative at prayer; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1025 (Box 11)
    - Yahia elders and friends at wedding; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1026 (Box 11)
    - Guests at Yahia wedding; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1027 (Box 11)
    - Guest at Yahia wedding; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1028 (Box 11)
    - Guest at Sakina Yahia's wedding; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1029 (Box 11)